<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Vasaz</author>
  <title>Welcome to ZaszBlog</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;
If you see this post it means that&amp;nbsp;ZaszBlog is up and running. Now the only thing that remains is for you to get in and start talking to the world. There are features to explore and take advantage of, for those who&amp;#39;re inquisitive. Now this will soon become full version, till then please feel free to try out anything&amp;nbsp;and all. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Permission to address the world&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
To be able to log in to the blog and writing posts, you need to get yourself an account, this can be done by sending me an email. All of the CSE &amp;#39;A&amp;#39; TCE class students, and some of the old-timers&amp;nbsp;will have one account by the time this comes out of beta. This is where you can put up anything you know or would like to know, anything at all that would give you life on the Internet. Beta-testers you can download the entire source for this website, for now its given as a link, which i update after every revision, soon you can use the svn repository directly, soon as the proper arrangements are made with the Web Host. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Posts &amp;amp; Pages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Find the sign-in link located either at the bottom of the page and click it. Put in your username and password, which you ought to know, if your account was created by email to me, then you will or would&amp;#39;ve been given your credentials also by mail.&amp;nbsp;Now you can use the Control Panel to create your posts and pages. These will be exposed to all users of the&amp;nbsp;Internet, and subject to commenting, if what you created was a post. &amp;nbsp;Pages are just static information, which you can use to upload your photos, or software, or projects you&amp;#39;re working on, and so on. You design them anyway you like and you will see link to it on the home page after you have created it. You can use any html editor(Frontpage, Publisher) to create your pages, and put in the html here. Create as many as you would like and organize them if needed setting Parent-Child settings. You can later link to these pages in any post or comment here, or practically from anywhere else from the internet(mail, blog, forum, etc.) 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;On the web &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
You can find&amp;nbsp;other details on the &lt;a href="/ThonZNet/ZaszBlog/Admin/Pages/www.thon.net" title="Thon"&gt;official&lt;/a&gt; website. Here you&amp;#39;ll find tutorials, documentation, tips and tricks and much more. The ongoing development of&amp;nbsp;this website&amp;nbsp;can be followed at said site where the daily builds will be put up. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Good luck and happy writing. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The&amp;nbsp;ZaszBlog Admin 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2008-04-22 00:00:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2008-04-23 19:01:40</lastModified>
  <raters>3</raters>
  <rating>4.4</rating>
  <slug>Welcome-to-ZaszBlog</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>blog</tag>
    <tag>welcome</tag>
    <tag>zaszblog</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments>
    <comment id="bb6ddd49-22b9-437c-a176-ad31d2b269ea" approved="True">
      <date>2008-04-20 16:37:25</date>
      <author>Chandru</author>
      <email>chandru9279@gmail.com</email>
      <ip>127.0.0.1</ip>
      <website>http://www.thon.net/</website>
      <content>Check out the monster avatars! Its based on the MonsterID HttpHandler by Alexander Schuc http://blog.furred.net/page/MonsterID-Demo.aspx and all users will be given an avatar = A Monster created from the Email ID.</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories>
    <category>914c30a5-7cad-46e9-b744-e7601e72da77</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>